Main Navigation:
1. Food delivery (Section 1)
2. How it works (Section 3)
3. Our cities (Section 4)
4. Sign up (Section 6)

Section 0: Header with hero image and navigation
Title: None

Goodbye junk food. Hello super healthy meals.
Button 1: I'm hungry (go down to sign up section)
Button 2: Show me more (go down to next section)


Section 1: Features
Title: Get food fast - not fast food.

Hello, we're Omnifood, your new premium food delivery service. We know you're always busy. No time for cooking. So let us take care of that, we're really good at it, we promise!

Up to 365 days/year
Never cook again! We really mean that. Our subscription plans include up to 365 days/year coverage. You can also choose to order more flexibly if that's your style.

Ready in 20 minutes
You're only twenty minutes away from your delicious and super healthy meals delivered right to your home. We work with the best chefs in each town to ensure that you're 100% happy.

100% organic
All our vegetables are fresh, organic and local. Animals are raised without added hormones or antibiotics. Good for your health, the environment, and it also tastes better!

Order anything
We don't limit your creativity, which means you can order whatever you feel like. You can also choose from our menu containing over 100 delicious meals. It's up to you!


Section 2: Favourite meals
Title: None

1. Korean bibimbap with egg and vegetables
2. Simple italian pizza with cherry tomatoes
3. Chicken breast steak with vegetables 
4. Autumn pumpkin soup
5. Paleo beef steak with vegetables
6. Healthy baguette with egg and vegetables
7. Burger with cheddar and bacon
8. Granola with cherries and strawberries

(see image numbers in the assets folder)

Section 3: How it works
Title: How it works - Simple as 1, 2, 3

1. Choose the subscription plan that best fits your needs and sign up today.
2. Order your delicious meal using our mobile app or website. Or you can even call us!
3. Enjoy your meal after less than 20 minutes. See you the next time!



Section 4: Cities
Title: We're currently in these cities

Lisbon
1600+ happy eaters
60+ top chefs
@omnifood_lx

San Francisco
3700+ happy eaters
160+ top chefs
@omnifood_sf

Berlin
2300+ happy eaters
110+ top chefs
@omnifood_berlin

London
1200+ happy eaters
50+ top chefs
@omnifood_london


Section 5: Customer testimonials
Title: Our customers can't live without us

Omnifood is just awesome! I just launched a startup which leaves me with no time for cooking, so Omnifood is a life-saver. Now that I got used to it, I couldn't live without my daily meals!
(Alberto Duncan)

Inexpensive, healthy and great-tasting meals, delivered right to my home. We have lots of food delivery here in Lisbon, but no one comes even close to Omifood. Me and my family are so in love!
(Joana Silva)

I was looking for a quick and easy food delivery service in San Franciso. I tried a lot of them and ended up with Omnifood. Best food delivery service in the Bay Area. Keep up the great work!
(Milton Chapman)


Section 6: Sign up and pricing plans
Title: Start eating healthy today

Plan 1: Premium
399$ per month
That's only 13.30$ per meal
1 meal every day
Order 24/7
Access to newest creations
Free delivery


Plan 2: Pro
149$ per month
That's only 14.90$ per meal
1 meal 10 days/month
Order 24/7
Access to newest creations
Free delivery


Plan 3: Starter
19$ per meal
1 meal
Order from 8 am to 12 pm
Free delivery

Section 7: Contact form
Title: We're happy to hear from you

Fields to include:
Name
Email
How did you find us?
Newsletter
Drop us a line

Section 8: Footer
Title: None

Navigation:
1. About us
2. Blog
3. Press
4. iOS App
5. Android App

Also include links to facebook, twitter, google+ and Instagram accounts.
